Los Angeles Institute of Contemporary Art
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Exhibitions and Programs, 1974-1987, Series 5:; (Boxes 3-13; 9.5 linear feet)
  - Exhibition Files, 1974-1987, 5.2
    - Exhibitions and Presentations, March 1976-April 1976 (Box 3, Folder 56)
      Robert Cumming, Allan Kaprow, William Leavitt, Allen Ruppersberg, Ed Ruscha
    - Imagination, April 1976-May 1976, (2 folders) (Box 3, Folder 57-58)
      Curated by Llyn Foulkes
    - Willoughby Sharp, April 1976 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Eighteen Bay Area Artists, May 1976-June 1976 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Richard Berger
      Cheryl Olsen Bowers
      Victor Cohen-Stuart
      Carol Eckman
      Kathy Goodell
      Anya Horvath
      David Ireland
      Bruce Johnson
      Vincent Lynch
      David Maclay
      Cherie Raciti
      Dorothy Reid
      Gregg Renfrow
      Jock Reynolds
      Mary Anne Rose
      Rudy Serra
      William Wareham
      John Woodall
    - Reflections on the Birth of Venus, Mar. 1976-Apr. 1976 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      Ulrike Rosenbach
    - Tops, May 1976 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      Tom Jenkins
    - Lou Nova, June 1976 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Two Exhibitions- Barbara Munger and Guy Williams, July 1976 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Jerry Anderson and Margaret Nielsen, August 1976-September 1976 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Joan Snyder, August 1976-September 1976 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Fred Eversley, September 1976-December 1976 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Five Artists and Their Fashions, September 1976 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      Chance and Loretta, Dabi, *LA*, Paula Sweet, Susan Sandhaus for B. Noel
    - Four Solo Exhibitions, September 1976-October 1976 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      Nancy Genn, John Okulick, Jack Scott, Leo Valledor
    - Exposing: Photographic Definitions, October 1976-December 1976 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      Michael Andrews
      Lewis Baltz
      Gary Burns
      Jo Ann Callis
      Darryl Curran
      Lou Brown Di Giulio
      John Divola
      Ronald Dunlap
      Judy Fiskin
      Robert Flick
      Vida Freeman
      Susan Haller
      Robert Heinecken
      Suda House
      Phil Jones
      Steve Kahn
      Waldemar Kalinowski
      Ben Lifson
      Jerry McMillan
      Marion Palfi
      Leland Rice
      Kay Shuper
      Edwin Sievers
      H. Arthur Taussig
      Robert Von Sternberg
      Edmund Teske
      Max Yavno
    - In Transit, October 1976 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      Vito Acconci, Kevin Boyle, Roger Webster, Martha Wilson
    - Cease to Exist, November 1976 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      COUM
    - Contempo Art Lecture, December 1976 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      Jimmie West
    - L.A. Tune-Up: Three Solo Dances, December 1976 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      Cathy Kerr
    - LAICA '76: a Retrospective, December 1976 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Stephen Seemayer, December 1976 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Michael Asher, David Askevold, and Richard Long, January 1977-February 1977 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - 100+, March 1977-April 1977 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Barry Markowitz, April 1977 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - John White, April 1977 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Foundations in Clay, May 1977-June 1977 (Box 4, Folder 22)
      Michael Frimkess
      John Mason
      Jim Melchert
      Ron Nagle
      Kenneth Price
      Paul Soldner
      Peter Voulkos
    - Southland Video Project Part II, May 1977-June 1977 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Southland Video Project Part IV, May 1977-June 1977 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Scott Grieger, May 1977-June 1977 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Stay Hungry, May 1977 (Box 4, Folder 26)
      Klaus Mettig, Katharina Sieverding
    - A Byte at the Opera, June 1977 (Box 4, Folder 27)
      Jim Pomeroy, Paul De Marinis
    - Evidence, June 1977-July 1977 (Box 4, Folder 28)
      Mike Mandel, Larry Sultan
    - Sightseeing, June 1977 (Box 4, Folder 29)
      Stephen Laub
    - Beeldend Theatre Amsterdam, July 1977 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Ed Newell and Lewis Palmer, July 1977-September 1977 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - The Fab Two, July 1977 (Box 4, Folder 32)
      Bob and Bob
    - A Point of View, Jul 1977-September 1977 (Box 4, Folder 33)
      Karen Carson, Barbara Kasten, Astrid Preston, Karen Wolff
    - Subtle Pleasures Pass Between Us, July 1977 (Box 4, Folder 34)
      Michelle Miller
    - They Turned and Swooped and Fell Into the grace and Force of Gravity Itself, July 1977 (Box 4, Folder 35)
      Shirley Henderson
    - Mark Keiserman, August 1977 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Narrative Themes/Audio Works, August 1977-October 1977 (Box 4, Folder 37)
      Laurie Anderson
      John Baldessari
      Nancy Blanchard
      Guy De Cointet
      Fern Friedman
      Terri Hanlon
      Barbara Kruger
      Bob Wilhite
    - Live From L.A., September 1977-October 1977 (Box 4, Folder 38)
      Richard Newton, Bradley Smith, Bob Wilhite
    - Meager Expectations, September 1977 (Box 4, Folder 39)
      Nancy Buchanan
    - Silver See, September 1977 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Vice, September 1977 (Box 4, Folder 41)
      Brian Dailey
    - LAICA: Room For Rant, October 1977 (Box 4, Folder 42)
      William Alan Morrison
    - Travel Log, October 1977 (Box 4, Folder 43)
      Norma Jean Deak
    - Southland Video Anthology Part V, November 1977-January 1978 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Unstretched Surfaces, November 1977-December 1977 (Box 4, Folder 45)
      Bernadette Bour
      Jerrold Burchman
      Thierry Delaroyere
      Daniel Dezeuze
      Charles Christopher Hill
      Christian Jaccard
      Allan McCollum
      Jean-Michel Meurice
      Jean-Pierre Pincemin
      Peter Plagens
      Tom Wudl
      Richard Yokomi
    - Andrew Wilf, November 1977 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Flesh and Form, December 1977 (Box 4, Folder 47)
      Jerry Burchard, Arne Lewis, Craig Morey, Arthur Ollman, Abigail Perlmutter
    - Interactive Video, December 1977-January 1978 (Box 4, Folder 48)
      Wendy Clarke
    - Architectural Views, Physical Facts, Psychic Effects, January 1978-February 1978 (Box 4, Folder 49)
      Richard Aldreidge, Fred Fisher, Craig Hodgetts, Coy Howard, Eugene Kupper, Robert Mangurian
    - Hazel Slawson and Bruce Wallin, January 1978 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Artwords and Bookworks, February 1978-March 1978 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Out of Necessity, February 1978 (Box 4, Folder 52)
      Elaine Hartnett
    - Jean-Marie Straub, February 1978 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Zeu, February 1978 (Box 4, Folder 54)
      Gloria Kisch
    - Peter Barton, March 1978 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Joe Deal, March 1978 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Public Domain/Private Shadows, March 1978-May 1978 (Box 4, Folder 57)
      Susan Amon
      Nancy Angelo
      Candace Compton
      Los Angeles Women's Communications Collective
      Gail Lorien
      Jean Mansour
      Susan Mogul
      Rosa Morales
      Martha Rosler
      Sally Shapiro
      Suzanne Shelton
      Vampire Video
      Visual Communications
    - Pat Hogan, April 1978-May 1978 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Kim Jones, Paul McCarthy, Linda Motano, and Martha Rosler, December 1977-January 1978 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Suzanne Lacy, April 1978 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Orgies Mysteries Theatre, April 1978 (Box 4, Folder 61)
      Hermann Nitsch
    - Pictures, April 1978- May 1978 (Box 4, Folder 62)
      Troy Brauntuch, Jack Goldstein, Sherrie Levine, Robert Longo, Philip Smith; curated by Douglas Crimp
    - Statements and Drawings, April 1978-May 1978 (Box 4, Folder 63)
      Jeffrey Vallance
    - A Museum of Drawers, May 1978-June 1978 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Susan Kaiser Vogel, May 1978 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Made in L.A., June 1978 (Box 4, Folder 66)
      Joyce Neimans
    - Short Plays For a Man on the Moon and the Teachings of John Brown in Florida, June 1978 (Box 4, Folder 67)
      Michael Myers
    - Simone Porti and Peter Van Riper, June 1978 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Fifteen Artists, July 1978-August 1978 (Box 4, Folder 69)
      Bob Ackerman
      Roy Bravo
      John Caldwell
      Dorit Cypis
      C. Joe Fay
      Gines Guillen
      Kelly Hames
      Kathy Kauffman
      Mike Kelley
      Barbara Marfori
      Sandra Mendelsohn-Rubin
      Tony Oursler
      Cathe Ruane
      Paul Tzanetepoulos
    - William T. Anderson and Ralph Conners, July 1978 (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - Before the Cock Crows You Will Deny Me Thrice, August 1978 (Box 4, Folder 71)
      Eiko and Koma
    - Robert Mapplethorpe, August 1978 (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - John Divola, September 1978 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Three Europeans: Polar Crossings, September 1978-October 1978, (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 2-3)
      Richard Kriesche, Gina Pane, Petr Stembera
    - William Brice, October 1978-November 1978 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Charles Kessler, October 1978-November 1978 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Magnetism, October 1978 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Don Button
      Lize Cain
      Verni Greenfield
      Cathy Karen
      Nancy Mock
      John McBurney
      Su McLane
      William Ranson
    - Stephen Seemayer, October 1978 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Video Plus, October 1978-January 1979 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      Eleanor Antin, John Sturgeon, Allan Kaprow, John Baldessari
    - Women Artists in Support of Women Candidates, October 1978 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      Lita Albuquerque
      Diane Destiny
      Channa Horowitz
      Nancy Kent
      Margaret Nielson
      Shirley Pettibone
      Daniela Quinn
      Marion Siciliano
      Paula Sweet
    - Joseph Cornell, December 1978 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Installations, December 1978-January 1979 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      Ellen Brooks, Cherie Raciti, Dorothy Reid, Ursula Schneider
    - Jimmie West, Bruce Fier, Kelsey Walker, December 1978 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Memorial Exhibition in Honor of Marion Palfi, December 1978-January 1979 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - The Arousing, January 1979 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      Rachel Rosenthal
    - Unveiling a Web, January 1979 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      Donna Henes
    - Richard Alpert, February 1979-March 1979 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Cancellation Proofs, February 1979-March 1979 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Jasper Johns and Ed Ruscha
    - Real Angelinos, February 1979-March 1979 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      Hildegarde Duane and Ilene Segalove
    - Robert Therrien, February 1979-March 1979 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Woods Davy, March 1979 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Down in the Rec Room, March 1979 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      Michael Smith
    - Reading, March 1979 (Box 5, Folder 22)
      Barbara Jo Revelle
    - Ron Linden and Gwinn Murrill, March 1979-April 1979 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Alan Sondheim, March 1979-April 1979 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Homage to Odilon Redon, April 1979 (Box 5, Folder 25)
      Sandra Binion
    - James Hayward, Peter Lodato, John McLaughlin, April 1979-May 1979 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Don Johnson, April 1979 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Paul McCarthy, May 1979 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Paul McCarthy, May 1979-June 1979 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Clothing Constructions, June 1979, (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 30-31)
      Karen Carson
      Shirley Karki
      Robert Kushner
      Kim MacConnel
      Pat Oleszko
      Jody Pinto
      Gregory Poe
      Judith Shea
      Victoria Star
      Richard Tuttle
      Bob Watts
      Jeff Way
    - Peter De Lory, June 1979 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Sentimental Fables, June 1979 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Sex is Stupid, June 1979 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - John Sturgeon, June 1979 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - 10 Artists, June 1979-July 1979 (Box 5, Folder 36)
      Geralyn Donohue
      Ulrike Hainle
      Laura Hayes
      Ulysses Jenkins
      John Miller
      Don West
      Robert Williamson
      Bruce Winn
      Bruce Yonemoto
    - David Seidner, July 1979 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Sound, July 1979-August 1979, (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 38-39)
    - CETA Arts Program at LAICA, August 1979 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Los Angeles/Toronto Exchange Show, August 1979-September 1979 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - A Tribute to Dolores Hart, September 1979 (Box 5, Folder 42)
      Simone Gad
    - L.A. Issue, September 1979 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Social Works, September 1979-October 1979, (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 44-45)
      Judy Baca
      Newton and Helen Harrison
      Leslie Labowitz
      Suzanne Lacy
      Fred Lonidier
      Bonnie Sherk
      Jim Woods
    - Timothy App, October 1979 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Four Canadians, October 1979-December 1979 (Box 5, Folder 47)
      Susan Britton, Colin Campbell, Lisa Steele, Clive Robertson
    - One of a Kind, October 1979-December 1979 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Autumn Sonata, November 1979-December 1979 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Canadian Creative Music Collective, November 1979 (Box 5, Folder 50)
      Peter Anson, Nobuo Kubota, Allan Mattes, Michael Snow, Casey Sokol
    - Robert Overby, November 1979 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Forget Everything You Know, December 1979 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Infinite Gold Void, December 1979-January 1980 (Box 5, Folder 53)
      Eric Orr
    - Chuck Lowry, December 1979 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Michelangelo Pistoletto, December 1979-January 1980, (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 55-56)
    - Survey Australia, December 1979-January 1980 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Jay Phillips, circa 1980s (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Al Payne, January 1980 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Carl Toth, January 1980 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - David Douke, February 1980 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - A Song She Sang to Herself, February 1980-March 1980 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Tableau, February 1980-March 1980 (Box 5, Folder 63)
      Julie Ann Bozzi
      Chris Burden
      Carl Cheng
      Ros Cross
      Phil Garner
      Bruce Houston
      The Kipper Kids
      Mark Lere
      Bill Leavitt
      Chip Lord
      Mickey McGowan
      Michael McMillan
      Nancy Reese
      David Sanderson
    - Cho Kawai, Richard Yokomi, Joan Watanabe, March 1980-April 1980 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Albano Guatti, March 1980 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - John Dorrs, Rita Myers, and Amy Taubin, March 1980 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Carol Kaufman, March 1980 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - David Lamelas, March 1980-May 1980 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Barry Le Va, March 1980-April 1980 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Loose Shorts, March 1980-May 1980 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      Coleen Sterritt
    - Peter Van Riper, March 1980 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Joan Watanabe, March 1980-April 1980 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Peter Alexander, April 1980-June 1980 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - William Larson, April 1980 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Pat Patterson, April 1980-June 1980 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Jill Giegrich, May 1980 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Jennifer Griffiths, May 1980 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Joan Jonas, May 1980 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - No Holds Barred, May 1980-June 1980 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      L.A. Dada
    - Carl Stone, May 1980 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Francesc Torres, May 1980-June 1980 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Abstract Paintings 1980, June 1980 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      Edith Bauman-Hidson, Scott Heywood, Penny Krebs, Alan Wayne, Stephan Westfall
    - Tony Conrad, June 1980 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Eight Seattle Artists, June 1980-July 1980 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      Jeffrey Bishop
      Keith Beckley
      Dennis Evans
      Carolyn Law
      Charles Luce
      Nancy Mee
      Mary Ann Peters
      Norie Sato
    - Kenneth McGowan, June 1980 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Plant War, June 1980-August 1980 (Box 6, Folder 23)
      Kim Jones
    - Gail Skoff, June 1980 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Buddy Collette, July 1980 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Shiro Ikegawa, July 1980-August 1980 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Nan Hoover and Raul Marroquin, July 1980-September 1980 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Bart Thrall, July 1980 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Bird's Eye Bedroom, August 1980-September 1980 (Box 6, Folder 29)
      Al Aguilar
    - Tim Galfas, August 1980 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Painting Sculpture, August 1980 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      Vivian Kerstein, William Mahan, George Page, Jay Phillips
    - Architectural Sculpture, September 1980-November 1980, (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 32-33)
      Alice Adams
      Marisa Alexander
      Pat Acona
      Siah Armajani
      Alice Aycock
      Peter Berg
      Tony Berlant
      Melvin Charney
      Donna Dennis
      Rayomn Elozua
      Harriet Feigenbaum
      Jackie Ferrara
      Richard Fleischner
      Akiko Fujita
      Cristos Gianakos
      George Grant
      Lloyd Hamrol
      Suzanne Harris
      Audrey Hemenway
      Nancy Holt
      Michael Hurson
      Will Insley
      Cletus Johnson
      Don Johnson
    - Artists Working at LAICA, September 1980 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - De Ann Jennings, September 1980 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Rudy Perez, September 1980 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Portraits of Artists, September 1980 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Stuart Rapeport, September 1980 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Reesy Shaw, September 1980-October 1980 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Diane Blell, October 1980-November 1980 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Aloha A.M., November 1980 (Box 6, Folder 41)
      Kevin Boyle
    - Laurence Dreiband, November 1980-December 1980 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Brian Forrest, November 1980-December 1980 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Ron George, November 1980 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Earl Howard, November 1980 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - John Mandel, November 1980 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Luis Benedit, December 1980-January 1981 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Peter D'Agostino, December 1980-February 1981 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Constance De Jong, December 1980 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Susan Rawcliffe, December 1980 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Trungpa Rinpoche, December 1980 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Wolf Vostell, December 1980-January 1981, (3 folders) (Box 6, Folder 52-54)
    - Jerry Anderson, January 1981-February 1981 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Michael Levine, January 1981-February 1981 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Southern California Artists, January 1981-February 1981 (Box 6, Folder 57)
      Kim Abeles
      Robert Ackerman
      Richard Baker
      Joe Fay
      Jill Giegerich
      Kathryn Halbower
      Diana Hobson
      James Isermann
      Carol Kaufman
      Stephen Nowlin
    - Women's Performance Month, January 1981 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - Eiko and Koma, February 1981 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Llyn Foulkes, March 1981-April 1981 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Sandro Martini, March 1981-April 1981 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Mary Jones, April 1981 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Tomoharu Murakami and Satoru Shoji, April 1981-May 1981 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Eleanor Antin, May 1981-June 1981 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Barbara Mensch, May 1981 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Mobile Image, May 1981-July 1981 (Box 6, Folder 66)
      Kit Galloway, Sherrie Rabinowitz
    - John Wager-Schneider, May 1981 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - Humor in Art, June 1981-August 1981 (Box 6, Folder 68)
      Terry Allen
      Robert Arneson
      Walter Askin
      Clayton Bailey
      Karen Breschi
      Robert Colescott
      William Crutchfield
      Roy De Forest
      Irene Dogmatic
      Tom Foolery
      Scott Grieger
      George Herms
      Robert Hudson
      Harry Lynn Krizan
      Madam X
      Michael Maglich
      Gary Martin
      Michael McMillen
      Gifford Meyers
      David Middlebrook
      Margaret Nielsen
      Irving Norman
      Gary Panter
      Pierre Picot
      Mel Ramos
      Roland Reiss
      Tom Rippon
      Ed Ruscha
      Ben Sakoguchi
      Terry Schoonhoven
      Louise Stanley
      Michael Stevens
      Masami Teraoka
      William T. Wiley
      Robert Yarber
    - Milano Kazanjian, June 1981 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - Stephen Pearson, June 1981 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - Nancy Reese, June 1981 (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - The Great Confrontation, August 1980 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      Douglas Hall
    - Gilbert Johnquest, July 1981 (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - Laura Lansworth, August 1981 (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - Paul Tzanetopoulos, August 1981 (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - Judy Fiskin, September 1981 (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - Vice, September 1981 (Box 6, Folder 77)
    - Wallpaper/Roompaper, September 1981-October 1981 (Box 6, Folder 78)
      Zigi Ben-Haim
      Lynda Benglis
      Wayne Hazen
      Neda Al-Hilali
      Charles Hilger
      Steve Jennis
      Patty Sue Jones
      Diane Katsiaficas
      Anne Flaten Pixley
      Elizabeth Shipley
      Angelica Sotiriou
      Steve Wood
    - Carole Caroompas, October 1981 (Box 6, Folder 79)
    - Leroy Neiman and Andy Warhol, November 1981-January 1982, (4 folders) (Box 6, Folder 80-83)
    - Al Ruppersberg, Patricia Ferris, Ronald In T'Hout, January 1982-February 1982 (Box 6, Folder 84)
    - Roy Dowell, January 1982-February 1982 (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Ilona Granet, February 1982 (Box 6, Folder 86)
    - Three Rooms, Three Views, March 1982-April 1982 (Box 6, Folder 87)
      Lois Colette, Marc Pally, Astrid Preston
    - Steve Galloway, May 1982-June 1982 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - James Bay Project, May 1982-June 1982 (Box 7, Folder 2-3)
      Claus Biegert, Rainer Wittenborn
    - David Lawson, June 1982-July 1982 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Canvassing L.A., July 1982-August 1982 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Patti Oleon, July 1982-August 1982 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Clytie Alexander, August 1982-September 1982 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Kady Hoffman, September 1982-October 1982 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Jeffrey Vallance and Stephen Seemayer, September 1982-October 1982 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Tom Wolf, September 1982-October 1982 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Kevin Boyle, October 1982-November 1982 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Laddie John Dill and James Kenney, October 1982-November 1982 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - J. Scott Riker, October 1982-November 1982 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Yura Adams, November 1982 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Bruce Everett, November 1982-December 1982 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Raul Guererro, November 1982-December 1982 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Manipulative Photography, November 1982-December 1982 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Richard Sigmund, November 1982-December 1982 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Alfredo Nunez, December 1982, (2 folders) (Box 7, Folder 19-20)
    - Changing Trends: Content and Style, January 1983-February 1983 (Box 7, Folder 21)
      Caron Colvin
      Marvin Harden
      James Hayward
      Ron Linden
      George Rodart
      Don Suggs
      David Trowbridge
    - Allen Harrison, January 1983-February 1983 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Dennis Parkhurst, January 1983-February 1983 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - War Games, January 1983-February 1983 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Jeff Gambill, March 1983-April 1983 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Steve Galloway and Jim Ganzer, March 1983-April 1983 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Laura Lasworth, March 1983-April 1983 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Amanda Jaffe, April 1983-May 1983 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Kharlene Boxenbaum, Scott Grieger, Megan Williams, Jeffrey Vallance, April 1983-May 1983 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Performances For the Blind, April 1983 (Box 7, Folder 30)
      Carole Caroompas, John White
    - Matt Roberts, April 1983-May 1983 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Jack Balas, June 1983-July 1983 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Tad Savinar, June 1983-July 1983 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - 10-10-10, June 1983-July 1983, (2 folders) (Box 7, Folder 34-35)
      Ali Acerol
      Clytie Alexander
      David Amico
      Charles Arnoldi
      Kyoko Asano
      Wallace Berman
      Diane Buckler
      Linda Burnham
      Lois Colette
      Katy Crowe
      Lavi Daniel
      Miriam Feldman
      Edward Gilliam
      Allen Harrison
      Roger Herman
      Michael Hogarth
      Karla Klarin
      Tom Knechtel
      Masayuki Oda
      Craig O'Rourke
      Renee Petropoulos
      Matthew Roberts
      Steve Rogers
      Monique Safford
      Stephen Sotnick
      Russel Tamblyn
      Janet Tholen
      Tim Valdez
      Norton Wisdom
    - Garrison Roots, Richard Roehl, and Vignir Johnannson, August 1983, (3 folders) (Box 7, Folder 36-38)